(Amy:)Forget it.
I don't expect you guys to understand.
(Raj:)I understand.
In seventh grade, I played spin-the-bottle
and it landed on Alina Shankar.
(Raj:)She said if I came near her,
she would break the bottle and cut me.
(Amy:)You think that's bad?
(Amy:)In college, I passed out at a frat party
and woke up with more clothes on.
Sometimes I get so Ionely I sit
on my left hand until it goes numb...
(Raj:)...then I put it in my right hand and pretend
I'm holding hands with another person.
(Amy:)I do that too.
(Amy:)Sometimes the left hand tries
to cop a feel.
(Amy:)And I let it.
(Raj:)It's kind of nice to talk to someone who
understands what it feels like to be alone.
(Amy:)It is, isn't it?
(Raj:)But you're not alone anymore.
Now you've got Sheldon.
(Amy:)I do. And don't worry,
someday you'll have somebody too.
(Raj:)Thank you. I hope she's half as lovely
and amazing as you are.